Guide to the New Dramatists Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Script Library, 1931-1985; Series I; 39.17; (32 boxes)
  - Helfer, Richard
    - A Dream of Freedom, undated (Box 13)
  - Hennefeld, Edmund B.
    - Darkness Called Night, undated (Box 13)
    - The Glass Hill, undated (Box 13)
    - Winter Harvest, undated (Box 13)
  - Herlihy, James Leo and Noble, William
    - Blue Denim, undated (Box 13)
  - Herlihy, James Leo
    - Moon in Capricorn, 1950 (Box 13)
  - Higley, Philo
    - The Flying Shadow, undated (Box 14)
    - The Princess Incident, 1954 (Box 14)
  - Hillard, Shirley
    - The Mole (2 copies), 1984 (Box 14)
  - Hirson, Roger O.
    - Untitled Musical Based on Hobson's Choice (musical), undated (Box 14)
    - Walking Happy (musical), undated (Box 14)
    - WW II & ½ (2 Plays-A Wicked, Wicked Woman; Someone's Been Sleeping in My Bed), undated (Box 14)
  - Horovitz, Israel
    - Line, undated (Box 14)
    - The World's Greatest Play, 1968 (Box 14)
  - Howard, David
    - Boy Wonder, undated (Box 14)
  - Hubbard, Haver
    - As the Wind Blows, undated (Box 14)
  - Huganir, Elma
    - Ceremony of Innocence, 1951 (Box 14)
  - Jeffries, Elizabeth
    - Half the World is a Bride, undated (Box 14)
  - Johnson, Cindy Lou
    - Moonya, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Jones, Kit
    - The Beholder, 1968 (Box 14)
    - Have Ya Seen Sean, undated (Box 14)
    - The Legacy, undated (Box 14)
    - The Tripple Bed (screenplay), 1976 (Box 14)
    - The Watch Pit, undated (Box 14)
  - Kagan, Diane
    - Marvelous Brown, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Kagan, Diane and Petrides, Avra
    - Phoebus, undated (Box 14)
    - Three Piece Band, undated (Box 14)
  - Kapner, Irving
    - The Morning of Our Years, undated (Box 14)
    - One of the Family, undated (Box 14)
  - Karchmer, Sylvan
    - The Honest Heart...The Knowing Head, undated (Box 14)
    - The Rose Garden, undated (Box 14)
    - A World of Flowers, undated (Box 14)
  - Kelman, Kenneth
    - Expiration (Simple Play #1), 1974 (Box 14)
    - Morality, 1971 (Box 14)
    - Scenes from Vampire Life, 1973 (Box 14)
  - Kerman, Sheppard
    - The Cut of the Ax, undated (Box 14)
    - The Dark and the Day, undated (Box 15)
    - Players on the Beach, undated (Box 15)
  - Khan, Faizul R. A.
    - The Shanty (2 copies), 1978 (Box 15)
  - Kierland, Joseph Scott
    - Drum-Taps, undated (Box 15)
  - Kierland, Jospeh Scott
    - The Egyptian Affair, undated (Box 15)
    - Hocus-Pocus, undated (Box 15)
    - Playsongs, undated (Box 15)
    - Sunday, undated (Box 15)
  - Killens, John Oliver and Mitchell, Loften
    - Ballad of the Winter Soldiers
  - Kinerk, Robert
    - Deutschland, undated (Box 15)
  - Klein, Grace and Cooper, Mae
    - Maggie
      See: Cooper, Mae, Box 6
  - Kliewer, Warren
    - The Berserkers, 1975 (Box 15)
    - The Booth Brothers, 1975 (Box 15)
    - Half Horse, Half Cockeyed Alligator, 1974 (Box 15)
    - A Lean and Hungry Priest (musical), 1973 (Box 15)
    - The Museum of Old Tyme Life, 1979 (Box 15)
    - The Two Marys, 1975 (Box 15)
  - Kramm, Joseph
    - The Shrike (2 copies), 1950 (Box 15)
  - Kuner, M. C.
    - Crown of Choice, 1951 (Box 15)
  - Lapica, Ray
    - The Broken String, 1953 (Box 15)
  - Lee, Leslie E.
    - Between Now and Then, 1974 (Box 15)
    - The Dead Autumn's Soul, 1974 (Box 15)
    - Killing Time, 1977 (Box 15)
    - Voices, 1975 (Box 15)
  - Lee, Leslie R.
    - The War Party, undated (Box 15)
  - Lemay, Harding
    - From a Dark Land, undated (Box 16)
    - The Heir-Apparent, undated (Box 16)
    - How I Became a Writer, 1980 (Box 16)
    - The Joslyn Circle, undated (Box 16)
    - The Little Birds Fly, undated (Box 16)
    - The Off Season, undated (Box 16)
    - Return Upriver (3rd Draft), undated (Box 16)
    - Shelter (musical), undated (Box 16)
    - The Wind that Blows, undated (Box 16)
  - Lessing, Norman
    - Citizen, undated (Box 16)
  - Levi, Stephen
    - Je t'aime, Jessica, undated (Box 16)
    - The Offering, undated (Box 16)
    - Today's Special, or Bombs on the ½-Shell (1st Draft), 1985 (Box 16)
  - Lewis, A. A.
    - A Beautiful Friendship, undated (Box 16)
    - Diplomatic Relations, undated (Box 16)
  - Lewis, Alfred Allen
    - For Art's Sake (musical), undated (Box 16)
  - Lewis, Allan
    - The Coral Beads, undated (Box 16)
  - Linney, Romulus
    - April Snow, undated (Box 16)
    - The Captivity of Pixie Shedman, 1981 (Box 16)
    - Childe Byron (manuscript), 1977 (Box 16)
    - Childe Byron (published) (2 copies), 1981 (Box 16)
    - Democracy of Esther (6 copies), undated (Box 16)
    - F. M., 1984 (Box 17)
    - Gardens of Eden (2 copies), 1982 (Box 17)
    - Laughing Stock (3 copies), 1984 (Box 17)
    - The Love Suicide at Schofield Barracks (3 copies), undated (Box 17)
    - Old Man Joseph & his Family, 1978 (Box 17)
    - Pops (5 copies), undated (Box 17)
    - Sand Mountain (3 copies), 1985 (Box 17)
    - Tennessee (2 copies), 1980 (Box 17)
    - 2 Legends-Soul of a Tree; Why the Lord Come to Sand Mountain (3 copies), undated (Box 17)
    - A Woman without a Name (3 copies), undated (Box 17)
  - Lipp, Frieda
    - A Nestless Bird, 1972 (Box 17)
    - The Party, 1971 (Box 17)
    - We Can't Imagine, 1971 (Box 17)
    - The Wolves and the Lambs, undated (Box 17)
    - Worlds, 1970 (Box 17)
  - Lippa, Louisa
    - Children, 1958 (Box 18)
    - Clytemnestra, 1958 (Box 18)
    - A House Remember, 1956 (Box 18)
  - Litz, Robert
    - Great Divide, undated (Box 18)
  - Locke, Sam
    - Wine at the Wedding, undated (Box 18)
  - Lord, Robert
    - Balance of Payments, undated (Box 18)
    - Bert and Maisy (2 copies), 1984 Nov 10 (Box 18)
    - China Wars, undated (Box 18)
    - Country Cops, 1986 Jan 1 (Box 18)
    - Country Cops, 1986 Jul 1 (Box 18)
    - Country Cops or Sharp or The Miller Murder Mystery (2 copies), 1985 (Box 18)
    - It Isn't Cricket (2 copies), undated (Box 18)
    - A Kite Play (High as a Kite), undated (Box 18)
    - The Most Valued Player, undated (Box 18)
    - The Traveling Squirrel, 1985 (Box 18)
    - The Traveling Squirrel-Tails of Manhattan, 1986 May 20 (Box 18)
    - The Traveling Squirrel-Tails of Manhattan, 1986 Aug 18 (Box 18)
  - Lowy, Bonnie Blue
    - The Half Lit World of a Later Day Homer, undated (Box 18)
    - A Lifetime Policy, undated (Box 18)
    - N, My Name is Nicki, undated (Box 18)
    - The Survivors, 1966 (Box 18)
  - Lynch, Martin
    - Minstrel Boys (5 copies), undated (Box 19)
  - Mabley, Edward H.
    - Bon Voyage (musical), undated (Box 19)
    - Dick Whittington and His Cat (symphonic story), 1966 (Box 19)
    - Doubleplay, undated (Box 19)
    - I Have a Dream (cantata), 1967 (Box 19)
    - The Mermaid in Lock #7 (musical), 1958 (Box 19)
    - Lyrics from various plays, undated (Box 19)
  - Mabley, Edward and Roos, Joanna
    - Borderline of Fear, undated (Box 19)
    - Red Sky at Morning, undated (Box 19)
    - The Twin Musicals (The Ascent of George W. Turtchell; No More Lovin') (musical), undated (Box 19)
  - Mack, C. K.
    - Esther, 1972 (Box 19)
    - The Family House, undated (Box 19)
    - Names, Numbers, and Other War Games, undated (Box 19)
    - A Safe Place, undated (Box 19)
    - The Survival Games, undated (Box 19)
  - Maher, Joseph
    - Dance for Me, Simeon, undated (Box 19)
  - Mamis, Jacob Enoch
    - A Cup for Elijah, undated (Box 19)
    - Who is This Guy Called God?, undated (Box 19)
  - Mamis, Justin E.
    - Apples and Innocence, undated (Box 19)
    - He'll Be Me, undated (Box 19)
    - The Oldest Profession, undated (Box 19)
    - The Winning of the West, undated (Box 19)
  - Manning, Phelps
    - The Sea Serpent, undated (Box 19)
    - The Death Wail of Mrs. Francis; McCafferty Smith & Silent Partner (2 plays), undated (Box 20)
  - Marmorstein, Malcolm
    - Keep the Pastrami Hot, undated (Box 20)
    - Ninnyhammers, undated (Box 20)
    - Will the Real Jesus Christ Please Stand Up?, undated (Box 20)
  - Martell, H. A.
    See: Appleman, H. A.
  - Mason, Cliff
    - Gabriel (The Story of a Slave Rebellion), undated (Box 20)
    - The Greatest Black Writer Who Ever Lived, 1976 (Box 20)
    - Jimmy X (The Story of a Young Boy), 1969 (Box 20)
    - Midnight Special, 1971 (Box 20)
    - Midnight Special-Notes, undated (Box 20)
    - Sister Sadie, undated (Box 20)
    - The Trial of Denmark Vessey, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Masteroff, Joe
    - Cabaret (second version)(musical)
      See: Welcome to Berlin
    - The Exorcist, undated (Box 20)
    - The Lexington Avenue Entrance, 1955 Nov 17 (Box 20)
    - Millions of George, 1953 (Box 20)
    - Run of the Play, undated (Box 20)
    - She Loves Me! (screenplay, musical), 1970 Nov 20 (Box 20)
      Screenplay, Musical
    - 60-Girls-60 (1st Draft), undated (Box 20)
    - Welcome to Berlin (1st Draft) (musical), undated (Box 20)
  - Max, Jerome
    - The Furthermost Finger of Fillmore, 1964 Aug (Box 20)
    - Hough in Blazes, undated (Box 20)
    - One of Us Has Been Ignited, undated (Box 20)
    - What Color Goes with Brown, 1964 (Box 20)
  - McGee, James
    - The Temptation of Maggy Haggerty (play with music), 1951 (Box 20)
  - McGhee-Anderson, Kathleen
    - Oak and Ivy, 1985 (Box 20)
  - McGlown, Jerry
    - The Quiet in the Land, 1984 (Box 20)
  - McGowan, John
    - The Dear Old Public, undated (Box 20)
    - Fireworks in the Sun, undated (Box 20)
    - The Miracle of Scraggly Top, 1949 (Box 21)
    - No Return, undated (Box 21)
    - None but Madmen, undated (Box 21)
    - Of All Things (Act One) (musical), 1931 May 6 (Box 21)
    - Say When (musical), undated (Box 21)
    - The Swordsman of Sutton Place, 1949 (Box 21)
    - Tenth Avenue (written with Lloyd Griscom), undated (Box 21)
    - Better 'N Gold (musical), undated (Box 21)
    - Excess Baggage, undated (Box 21)
    - Flowers for the Victim, 1954 (Box 21)
    - Like Most Ladies, undated (Box 21)
    - McKenna (short story), undated (Box 21)
    - Move Over, Baby, undated (Box 21)
    - No Kid!, undated (Box 21)
    - The Parade Passes, undated (Box 21)
    - The Primrose Touch (outline), undated (Box 21)
    - Singin' the Blues (musical), undated (Box 21)
    - Total Strangers (Act One), undated (Box 21)
    - You Can Go to Heaven (story), undated (Box 21)
  - McGowan, John and Dunning, Philip
    - The Last Song, undated (Box 21)
  - McGowan, John and Craig Jr., Richy
    - Pardon Me! (Act One), undated (Box 21)
  - McKinney, Gene
    - A Different Drummer (2 copies), 1955 (Box 21)
  - McLiam, John
    - The Sin of Pat Muldoon, undated (Box 21)
  - Meredith, Kevin
    - The Man with the Graph Shaped Like Your Stomach, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Meyer, Fred
    - The Days of the Fair, undated (Box 21)
    - Perfect Prince (musical), 1957 Jun 1 (Box 21)
    - Scandalous Acts, undated (Box 21)
  - Michaels, Sidney
    - The Elizabethans, 1972 (Box 21)
  - Miller, Maureen
    - Fake Out, undated (Box 21)
  - Miller, Sigmund
    - One Bright Day, undated (Box 21)
  - Misrock, Henry
    - God Had 7 Days, undated (Box 21)
  - Mitchell, Loften and Burgie, Irving
    - Ballad for Bimshire (musical), 1964 (Box 21)
  - Mitchell, Loften and Killens, John Oliver
    - Ballad of the Winter Soldiers, undated (Box 22)
  - Mitchell, Loften
    - City Called Harlem, undated (Box 22)
    - Gypsy Story, undated (Box 22)
    - Star of the Morning, 1961 (Box 22)
    - Tell Pharaoh, undated (Box 22)
  - Mollison, A. P.
    - Ami, Go Home, 1955 (Box 22)
    - Around Her Little Finger, 1955 (Box 22)
    - Edge of the Roof, 1953 (Box 22)
    - Lisa and the Lord, 1953 (Box 22)
    - Molka and the Commissar or Head Over Heart, 1954 (Box 22)
    - With Adjoining Cell, 1954 (Box 22)
  - Monjo, F. N.
    - The Vision; Grandfathers; The Bear (3 plays), undated (Box 22)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 22)
    - You Been a Good Old Wagon, Mamma Hespers, But You Done Broke Down, undated (Box 22)
  - Moore, Thomas F.
    - The Merry Chase, undated (Box 22)
  - Morris, Edmund
    - The Wooden Dish, undated (Box 22)
  - Morton, Frederic
    - Love in an Album, undated (Box 22)
  - Mosier, Frank Moffett
    - Christine Fonnegra, 1958 (Box 22)
    - The First Big River, undated (Box 22)
    - King for a Day, undated (Box 22)
    - The Naked Truth, undated (Box 22)
    - Two by Four-Come Up and See My Casserole; The Eagle and the Rock, undated (Box 22)
    - The Winter Soldier, undated (Box 22)
  - Muller, Romeo
    - Angel, with the Big, Big Ears, 1954 (Box 22)
    - Cedar Hill Park, undated (Box 22)
    - A Diamond Studded Kreplach (play with music) (Box 22)
      See also: ...Like Wonderful
    - The Great Git-Away, 1955 (Box 22)
    - ...Like Wonderful (play with music) (Box 22)
      See also: A Diamond Studded Kreplach
    - Pop Goes the Weasel, undated (Box 22)
  - Newman, Paul S.
    - The Coffee Bean, undated (Box 23)
  - Noble, William
    - Blue Denim
      See: Herlihy, James Leo, Box 13
    - Starfish, 1954 (Box 23)
  - Noel, Maurice
    - Girl of the Golden West, undated (Box 23)
  - O'Connell, Francis
    - But Two Can, 1982 (Box 23)
  - O'Donnell, Gene
    - The Long Whistle, 1952 Dec (Box 23)
    - Run, David, 1953 (Box 23)
  - O'Neill, Frances
    - Ball of Fire, undated (Box 23)
  - O'Reilly, Michael
    - Dance for a Naked Lady, undated (Box 23)
    - Dinner at the Ambassador's, 1972 (Box 23)
    - Mad on 42nd Street (screenplay), 1974 (Box 23)
  - O'Sullivan, Eugene and Sherman, Allan
    - The Happy Medium
  - Orlock, John
    - Revolution of the Heavenly Orbs, undated (Box 23)
  - Owens, Rochelle
    - Futz, undated (Box 23)
  - Parchman, William E.
    - Flower Pots on a Window Sill, undated (Box 23)
    - The Great Easter Egg Hunt, undated (Box 23)
    - Needmore, undated (Box 23)
    - Oh, the King of the Hill is Down, undated (Box 23)
    - Once in Arcadia, undated (Box 23)
    - The Party (play with music), undated (Box 23)
    - Play, undated (Box 23)
    - The Prize in the Cracker Jack Box, undated (Box 23)
    - Rosedew and Sin, undated (Box 23)
    - Score One (screenplay), undated (Box 23)
    - Mary Hamilton; Mocking Bird (2 plays), undated (Box 23)
    - Villon, undated (Box 23)
  - Perkins, Aveline
    - The Ghost Children, undated (Box 23)
    - His Wife Hath Learned to Kiss, undated (Box 23)
  - Perkins, Aveline and Perkins, Toby
    - The Iron Coronet, 1951 (Box 23)
  - Peters, Paul
    - The Age of the Fish, 1951 (Box 24)
    - Thursday's Child (2 copies), undated (Box 24)
  - Peterson, Don
    - The Enemy is Dead, 1968 (Box 24)
    - The Teacher's Meeting, undated (Box 24)
  - Petrides, Avra
    - Phoebus
      See: Kagan, Diane, Box 14
    - Soft Shoulders, undated (Box 24)
    - Three Piece Band
  - Pielmeier, John
    - Jass, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Pierson, Kenn
    - The Spirit of Saint Louis (2 copies), 1981 (Box 24)
  - Pittman, Arthur
    - Change, undated (Box 24)
    - Happiness (A Small Adjustment), undated (Box 24)
    - Notes from a New York Pawnshop, undated (Box 24)
    - Practical, undated (Box 24)
  - Radano, Gene
    - The Apple Doesn't Fall, undated (Box 24)
    - The Deadlock, undated (Box 24)
    - Even the Window is Gone, undated (Box 24)
    - Fly Away He Flew, undated (Box 24)
    - The Fourth Nail, undated (Box 24)
    - The Mute Who Sang, undated (Box 24)
    - The Tow Line, undated (Box 24)
    - The World is Yours, undated (Box 24)
  - Ramsey, Peter
    - Three Acts of Charity, undated (Box 24)
  - Raskin, Eugene
    - Amata, undated (Box 24)
    - The Old Friend, undated (Box 24)
    - One's a Crowd, 1953 (Box 24)
    - Mama Doll (monologue), undated (Box 24)
    - Onward, Viking!, undated (Box 24)
  - Rayfiel, David
    - P.S. 193, undated (Box 25)
  - Raynor, Sally
    - Cry Uncle, undated (Box 25)
    - Perhaps Pandora, undated (Box 25)
  - Reines, Bernard
    - The Country Gentleman, undated (Box 25)
  - Richardson, Howard and Gerber, Ella
    - The Idols and the Prey, undated (Box 25)
  - Richards, Howard and Goforth, Frances
    - Off the Record, 1952 (Box 25)
  - Ridgley, Harry
    - The Angry Apes, undated (Box 25)
    - Shivaree, undated (Box 25)
  - Rieser, Allen
    - Untitled, undated (Box 25)
  - Robertson, Milton
    - A Rainbow at Home, 1953 (Box 25)
    - Seven Day Wonder (musical), undated (Box 25)
  - Robins, Sam
    - The Wooden Pillow, undated (Box 25)
  - Romulus, Linney
    - The Captivity of Pixie Shedman, 1981 (Box 25)
  - Roos, Joanna
    - Among Ourselves, undated (Box 25)
  - Roos, Joanna and Mabley, Edward
    - Borderline of Fear, Red Sky at Morning, The Twin Musicals (3 plays)
      See: Mabley, Edward, Box 19
  - Rosa, Ben
    - Obtuse Triangle, 1971 (Box 25)
  - Ross, Sam
    - The Deal, 1956 (Box 25)
    - He Ran All the Way, 1954 (Box 25)
  - Rotenberg, Susan
    - Madie Ain't (musical), 1975 (Box 25)
  - Rubin, Mann
    - The Trees of Promise, undated (Box 25)
  - Rubio, Emery and Balf, Miriam
    - The Jeweler of Dale, undated (Box 25)
  - Rudd, Enid
    - The Ashes of Mrs. Reasoner, undated (Box 25)
    - Does Anybody Here Do the Peabody?, undated (Box 25)
    - What Do I Do About Hemingway?, undated (Box 25)
  - Rukeyser, Muriel
    - Houdini, undated (Box 25)
  - Ruscoll, Joseph and Essex, Harry
    - A Neighborhood Affair, undated (Box 25)
  - Ryan, Elaine
    - Lydia, undated (Box 25)
  - Sack, Louis
    - Blast Furnace, undated (Box 25)
    - Carnival in Silhouette, undated (Box 25)
  - Saffron, Robert and Gordon, George N.
    - Cellini Came from My Town (teleplay), undated (Box 25)
  - Saffron, Robert
    - The Magnificent Macinnes, undated (Box 26)
  - Savarese, Julia
    - Child's Play (2 copies), undated (Box 26)
    - Rosie, undated (Box 26)
  - Savcool, John K.
    - Ondine, undated (Box 26)
  - Scarbrough, Janeice
    - Trinity Site, 1985 (Box 26)
  - Schochen, Seyril
    - Afternoon at the Shore, undated (Box 26)
    - Blue Island, undated (Box 26)
    - The Moon Besieged, 1962 Apr 1 (Box 26)
  - Schoenwater, Sydney
    - The Golden Egg, undated (Box 26)
    - The House of Hartman, undated (Box 26)
  - Schnee, Thelma
    - Bedlam, 1949 (Box 26)
  - Scott, J. J.
    - Ride the Cockhorse, undated (Box 26)
  - Scott, Joseph
    - Amarantha, undated (Box 26)
    - The Minotaur, undated (Box 26)
    - The Snow of Southern Summer, undated (Box 26)
    - Sunday, undated (Box 26)
  - Selden, George
    - The Genie of Sutton Place (screenplay), 1962 Jan 21 (Box 26)
  - Seven, Marilyn
    - Double Dutch (2 copies), 1981 (Box 26)
  - Shanley, John Patrick
    - The Dreamer Examines His Pillow, 1985 (Box 26)
  - Sherman, Allan and Burtson, Bud
    - The Golden Touch (musical), undated (Box 26)
  - Sherman, Allan and O'Sullivan, Eugene
    - The Happy Medium, 1952 (Box 26)
  - Sherry, John
    - Abraham's Ghost, undated (Box 26)
  - Sherry, John
    - The Gunshot, undated (Box 26)
  - Shurtleff, Michael
    - Call Me By My Rightful Name, 1961 (Box 26)
    - Stella and the City Man, undated (Box 26)
    - Sweet Lunacy, undated (Box 27)
  - Smickes, Seymour
    - Seven Days of Mourning, undated (Box 27)
  - Sipherd, Ray
    - Joy to the World, undated (Box 27)
  - Smith, Conrad Sutton
    - Silence is Golden, 1957 (Box 27)
  - Smith, George Alan
    - The Comic Strip, undated (Box 27)
    - The White Steeple, undated (Box 27)
  - Snider, Richard
    - The Fife Played the Fool, 1950 (Box 27)
  - Snyder, William
    - The Days and Nights of Beebee Fenstermaker, 1962 (Box 27)
  - Stanley, Michael
    - The Myrmidon or The Scapegoat, 1951 (Box 27)
  - Stark, Sheldon
    - Time of Storm, 1954 (Box 27)
  - Staten, P. S.
    - Heartland, undated (Box 27)
  - Staten, Pat
    - The Scholar, undated (Box 27)
    - Twister, 1981 (Box 27)
  - Stavis, Barrie
    - The Man Who Never Died, 1959 (Box 27)
  - Stein, Sol
    - The Illegitimist, 1954 (Box 27)
    - Napoleon, 1952 (Box 27)
    - The Trouble with Shakespeare, 1961 (Box 27)
  - Stevens, Cass
    - The Small Woman, undated (Box 27)
  - Stevenson, Florence
    - The Chronicle of Nine, 1953 (Box 27)
    - Dark Odyssey, 1956 (Box 27)
    - The Key, 1956 (Box 27)
    - Pleasure Dome, 1954 (Box 27)
    - The Queen's Pawn, 1957 (Box 27)
    - Strumpet in Satin, 1953 (Box 27)
    - Three, 1957 (Box 27)
    - Witness, undated (Box 27)
  - Stovall, Miriam
    - An Owl in a Chinaberry Tree, undated (Box 27)
  - Symington, Donald
    - Family Affair, undated (Box 27)
    - The Golden Carpet, undated (Box 28)
  - Targovnick, Herbert
    - The Man of Action, undated (Box 28)
    - Song of Songs, 1952 (Box 28)
  - Tarrant, John
    - The Happy Porpoise, undated (Box 28)
    - Summer Night, undated (Box 28)
    - The Trappers and the Trapped (1st Draft), undated (Box 28)
  - Taub, Harold Jaedicker
    - Denny Malone (musical), undated (Box 28)
    - Four Lives, 1949 (Box 28)
  - Terpiloff, Anthony
    - Completely Foolproof (teleplay), 1964 Aug 4 (Box 28)
    - God is a Clown, 1958 (Box 28)
    - No Sometime Thing, undated (Box 28)
    - Spirit of the Dead Watches, 1958 (Box 28)
    - Those Rotten Golden Apples, undated (Box 28)
  - Terry, Megan
    - Hothouse, undated (Box 28)
    - Jack-Jack (musical), undated (Box 28)
    - The People vs. Ranchman, undated (Box 28)
  - Thom, Robert
    - Carnation, Lily, Lily, Rose, undated (Box 28)
    - The Minotaur, undated (Box 28)
    - Sailing to Byzantium, undated (Box 28)
    - The Sun-Dial, undated (Box 28)
  - Thompson, Carole Leslie
    - I'd Go to Heaven If I Was Good, 1970 (Box 28)
    - The Leftovers, undated (Box 28)
  - Thompson, Eric
    - Artists for the Revolution, undated (Box 28)
    - Atheist in a Foxhole, undated (Box 28)
    - Babylon, undated (Box 28)
    - Brooklyn Bridge (Act One), undated (Box 28)
    - The Enchanted Hudson, undated (Box 28)
    - Young Fellow-My-Lad, undated (Box 28)
  - Toscan, Richard
    - Just Another Country Song (1st draft), 1985 Apr 2 (Box 28)
  - Trainer, David
    - Skipping, undated (Box 28)
  - Turner, Dennis
    - Give My Regards to Broadway, undated (Box 29)
    - Nell (musical)
      See: Green, William, Box 12
    - The Rapists, undated (Box 29)
  - Vall, Seymour
    - The Long Long Rope, undated (Box 29)
    - The Reluctant Messiah, undated (Box 29)
    - Take the Devil's Hand, undated (Box 29)
  - Vane, N. Thaddeus
    - The Moon is a Clock, undated (Box 29)
  - Vaughan, Stuart
    - Assassination, 1865, undated (Box 29)
    - Favorites, 1977 (Box 29)
    - Ghost Dance, 1972 (Box 29)
    - Just Off Park, 1978 (Box 29)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 29)
    - Veil of Infamy, 1974 (Box 29)
  - Von Hartz, John
    - The Beach Children, undated (Box 29)
    - Mothers and Daughters, undated (Box 29)
    - The New Man, undated (Box 29)
    - Slum Love, undated (Box 29)
  - Von Klemm, V. Allen
    - Always the Running, 1953 (Box 29)
  - Wallsten, Robert
    - A Play About Lovers, undated (Box 29)
  - Waters, Marianne
    - The Swan Boat, undated (Box 29)
  - Weil, Raymond
    - Come Down, Daniel, 1951 (Box 29)
    - Comeuppance, undated (Box 29)
  - Weiner, Leslie
    - Arrival of Buyers, 1952 (Box 29)
    - Jolly Jolly Sixpence, 1954 (Box 29)
  - Weinstein, Arnold
    - The Party, 1963 (Box 29)
  - Welles, Violet
    - Aun, undated (Box 29)
    - The Girl, undated (Box 30)
    - The Spring Affair, undated (Box 30)
    - The Witch of the Wilderness, undated (Box 30)
  - Wexler, Norman
    - Lovers in the Act, undated (Box 30)
    - Private Opening, undated (Box 30)
    - Red's My Color, What's Yours?, undated (Box 30)
    - Rich on a Monday, undated (Box 30)
    - Take Another Thousand, It's Cheap, undated (Box 30)
  - Wiggam, Lionel
    - Bang, undated (Box 30)
    - Inside Emily Payne, undated (Box 30)
    - Siren Song, undated (Box 30)
  - Wilk, Max
    - Cloud Seven, 1958 (Box 30)
    - These are the Jokes, 1987 Sep (Box 30)
    - These are the Jokes, 1987 Feb (Box 30)
  - Williams, Bryan
    - In this Fallen City, 1985 (Box 30)
  - Wilson, August
    - Joe Turner's Come and Gone, undated (Box 30)
  - Wilson, Lanford
    - Angels Fall, 1983 (Box 30)